PRICES WERE LOWER FOR EVERYBODY UNTIL THE WAR, AND IT STILL REMAINS CLOSED, AND
PRICES WERE LOWER FOR EVERYBODY UNTIL THE WAR, AND IT STILL REMAINS CLOSED, AND TRAGICALLY,
UNTIL THE WAR, AND IT STILL REMAINS CLOSED, AND TRAGICALLY,
UNTIL THE WAR, AND IT STILL REMAINS CLOSED, AND TRAGICALLY, SERVICE
UNTIL THE WAR, AND IT STILL REMAINS CLOSED, AND TRAGICALLY, SERVICE MEMBERS,
UNTIL THE WAR, AND IT STILL REMAINS CLOSED, AND TRAGICALLY, SERVICE MEMBERS, OUR
UNTIL THE WAR, AND IT STILL REMAINS CLOSED, AND TRAGICALLY, SERVICE MEMBERS, OUR WAR
REMAINS CLOSED, AND TRAGICALLY, SERVICE MEMBERS, OUR WAR
REMAINS CLOSED, AND TRAGICALLY, SERVICE MEMBERS, OUR WAR FIGHTERS
REMAINS CLOSED, AND TRAGICALLY, SERVICE MEMBERS, OUR WAR FIGHTERS WHO
REMAINS CLOSED, AND TRAGICALLY, SERVICE MEMBERS, OUR WAR FIGHTERS WHO WE
REMAINS CLOSED, AND TRAGICALLY, SERVICE MEMBERS, OUR WAR FIGHTERS WHO WE CARE
REMAINS CLOSED, AND TRAGICALLY, SERVICE MEMBERS, OUR WAR FIGHTERS WHO WE CARE DEEPLY
SERVICE MEMBERS, OUR WAR FIGHTERS WHO WE CARE DEEPLY
SERVICE MEMBERS, OUR WAR FIGHTERS WHO WE CARE DEEPLY ABOUT
SERVICE MEMBERS, OUR WAR FIGHTERS WHO WE CARE DEEPLY ABOUT ARE
SERVICE MEMBERS, OUR WAR FIGHTERS WHO WE CARE DEEPLY ABOUT ARE STILL
SERVICE MEMBERS, OUR WAR FIGHTERS WHO WE CARE DEEPLY ABOUT ARE STILL DYING.
FIGHTERS WHO WE CARE DEEPLY ABOUT ARE STILL DYING.
FIGHTERS WHO WE CARE DEEPLY ABOUT ARE STILL DYING. WHAT
FIGHTERS WHO WE CARE DEEPLY ABOUT ARE STILL DYING. WHAT IS
FIGHTERS WHO WE CARE DEEPLY ABOUT ARE STILL DYING. WHAT IS DIFFERENT?
ABOUT ARE STILL DYING. WHAT IS DIFFERENT?
ABOUT ARE STILL DYING. WHAT IS DIFFERENT? >>
ABOUT ARE STILL DYING. WHAT IS DIFFERENT? >> I
ABOUT ARE STILL DYING. WHAT IS DIFFERENT? >> I THINK
ABOUT ARE STILL DYING. WHAT IS DIFFERENT? >> I THINK YOU
ABOUT ARE STILL DYING. WHAT IS DIFFERENT? >> I THINK YOU SAYING
ABOUT ARE STILL DYING. WHAT IS DIFFERENT? >> I THINK YOU SAYING IT
ABOUT ARE STILL DYING. WHAT IS DIFFERENT? >> I THINK YOU SAYING IT IS
ABOUT ARE STILL DYING. WHAT IS DIFFERENT? >> I THINK YOU SAYING IT IS A
WHAT IS DIFFERENT? >> I THINK YOU SAYING IT IS A
WHAT IS DIFFERENT? >> I THINK YOU SAYING IT IS A FAILURE
WHAT IS DIFFERENT? >> I THINK YOU SAYING IT IS A FAILURE IS
WHAT IS DIFFERENT? >> I THINK YOU SAYING IT IS A FAILURE IS A
WHAT IS DIFFERENT? >> I THINK YOU SAYING IT IS A FAILURE IS A RECKLESS.
>> I THINK YOU SAYING IT IS A FAILURE IS A RECKLESS.
>> I THINK YOU SAYING IT IS A FAILURE IS A RECKLESS. THE
>> I THINK YOU SAYING IT IS A FAILURE IS A RECKLESS. THE SACRIFICE
>> I THINK YOU SAYING IT IS A FAILURE IS A RECKLESS. THE SACRIFICE OF
>> I THINK YOU SAYING IT IS A FAILURE IS A RECKLESS. THE SACRIFICE OF TROOPS
>> I THINK YOU SAYING IT IS A FAILURE IS A RECKLESS. THE SACRIFICE OF TROOPS ARE
FAILURE IS A RECKLESS. THE SACRIFICE OF TROOPS ARE
FAILURE IS A RECKLESS. THE SACRIFICE OF TROOPS ARE MAKING
FAILURE IS A RECKLESS. THE SACRIFICE OF TROOPS ARE MAKING THAT
FAILURE IS A RECKLESS. THE SACRIFICE OF TROOPS ARE MAKING THAT IRAN
FAILURE IS A RECKLESS. THE SACRIFICE OF TROOPS ARE MAKING THAT IRAN NEVER
FAILURE IS A RECKLESS. THE SACRIFICE OF TROOPS ARE MAKING THAT IRAN NEVER GETS
FAILURE IS A RECKLESS. THE SACRIFICE OF TROOPS ARE MAKING THAT IRAN NEVER GETS A
THE SACRIFICE OF TROOPS ARE MAKING THAT IRAN NEVER GETS A
THE SACRIFICE OF TROOPS ARE MAKING THAT IRAN NEVER GETS A NUCLEAR
THE SACRIFICE OF TROOPS ARE MAKING THAT IRAN NEVER GETS A NUCLEAR WEAPON.
MAKING THAT IRAN NEVER GETS A NUCLEAR WEAPON.
MAKING THAT IRAN NEVER GETS A NUCLEAR WEAPON. SHAME
MAKING THAT IRAN NEVER GETS A NUCLEAR WEAPON. SHAME ON
MAKING THAT IRAN NEVER GETS A NUCLEAR WEAPON. SHAME ON YOU
MAKING THAT IRAN NEVER GETS A NUCLEAR WEAPON. SHAME ON YOU AND
MAKING THAT IRAN NEVER GETS A NUCLEAR WEAPON. SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS
MAKING THAT IRAN NEVER GETS A NUCLEAR WEAPON. SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND
MAKING THAT IRAN NEVER GETS A NUCLEAR WEAPON. SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND YOU
NUCLEAR WEAPON. SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND YOU
NUCLEAR WEAPON. SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND YOU WANT
NUCLEAR WEAPON. SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND YOU WANT TO
NUCLEAR WEAPON. SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND YOU WANT TO TURN
NUCLEAR WEAPON. SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND YOU WANT TO TURN AROUND
NUCLEAR WEAPON. SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND YOU WANT TO TURN AROUND AND
NUCLEAR WEAPON. SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND YOU WANT TO TURN AROUND AND SAY
NUCLEAR WEAPON. SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND YOU WANT TO TURN AROUND AND SAY YOU
SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND YOU WANT TO TURN AROUND AND SAY YOU
SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND YOU WANT TO TURN AROUND AND SAY YOU SUPPORT
SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND YOU WANT TO TURN AROUND AND SAY YOU SUPPORT THE
SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND YOU WANT TO TURN AROUND AND SAY YOU SUPPORT THE WAR
SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND YOU WANT TO TURN AROUND AND SAY YOU SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING
SHAME ON YOU AND OTHERS AND YOU WANT TO TURN AROUND AND SAY YOU SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING --
WANT TO TURN AROUND AND SAY YOU SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING --
WANT TO TURN AROUND AND SAY YOU SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING -- EITHER
WANT TO TURN AROUND AND SAY YOU SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING -- EITHER YOU
WANT TO TURN AROUND AND SAY YOU SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING -- EITHER YOU DO
WANT TO TURN AROUND AND SAY YOU SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING -- EITHER YOU DO OR
WANT TO TURN AROUND AND SAY YOU SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING -- EITHER YOU DO OR YOU
WANT TO TURN AROUND AND SAY YOU SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING -- EITHER YOU DO OR YOU DON'T.
SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING -- EITHER YOU DO OR YOU DON'T.
SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING -- EITHER YOU DO OR YOU DON'T. >>
SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING -- EITHER YOU DO OR YOU DON'T. >> IS
SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING -- EITHER YOU DO OR YOU DON'T. >> IS THE
SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING -- EITHER YOU DO OR YOU DON'T. >> IS THE NUCLEAR
SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING -- EITHER YOU DO OR YOU DON'T. >> IS THE NUCLEAR MATERIAL
SUPPORT THE WAR FIGHTING -- EITHER YOU DO OR YOU DON'T. >> IS THE NUCLEAR MATERIAL SO
EITHER YOU DO OR YOU DON'T. >> IS THE NUCLEAR MATERIAL SO
EITHER YOU DO OR YOU DON'T. >> IS THE NUCLEAR MATERIAL SO THERE?
>> IS THE NUCLEAR MATERIAL SO THERE?
>> IS THE NUCLEAR MATERIAL SO THERE? SEC.
>> IS THE NUCLEAR MATERIAL SO THERE? SEC. HEGSETH:
>> IS THE NUCLEAR MATERIAL SO THERE? SEC. HEGSETH: I
>> IS THE NUCLEAR MATERIAL SO THERE? SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN
>> IS THE NUCLEAR MATERIAL SO THERE? SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET
>> IS THE NUCLEAR MATERIAL SO THERE? SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET YOU
THERE? SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET YOU
THERE? SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET YOU THERE
THERE? SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET YOU THERE TO
THERE? SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET YOU THERE TO TALK
THERE? SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET YOU THERE TO TALK TO
THERE? SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET YOU THERE TO TALK TO THE
THERE? SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET YOU THERE TO TALK TO THE AMERICANS
SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET YOU THERE TO TALK TO THE AMERICANS
SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET YOU THERE TO TALK TO THE AMERICANS AND
SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET YOU THERE TO TALK TO THE AMERICANS AND HOW
SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET YOU THERE TO TALK TO THE AMERICANS AND HOW COMMITTED
SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET YOU THERE TO TALK TO THE AMERICANS AND HOW COMMITTED THEY
SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET YOU THERE TO TALK TO THE AMERICANS AND HOW COMMITTED THEY ARE
SEC. HEGSETH: I CAN GET YOU THERE TO TALK TO THE AMERICANS AND HOW COMMITTED THEY ARE TO
THERE TO TALK TO THE AMERICANS AND HOW COMMITTED THEY ARE TO
THERE TO TALK TO THE AMERICANS AND HOW COMMITTED THEY ARE TO THIS
THERE TO TALK TO THE AMERICANS AND HOW COMMITTED THEY ARE TO THIS EFFORT
THERE TO TALK TO THE AMERICANS AND HOW COMMITTED THEY ARE TO THIS EFFORT AND
THERE TO TALK TO THE AMERICANS AND HOW COMMITTED THEY ARE TO THIS EFFORT AND MAKING
THERE TO TALK TO THE AMERICANS AND HOW COMMITTED THEY ARE TO THIS EFFORT AND MAKING SURE
THERE TO TALK TO THE AMERICANS AND HOW COMMITTED THEY ARE TO THIS EFFORT AND MAKING SURE IRAN
AND HOW COMMITTED THEY ARE TO THIS EFFORT AND MAKING SURE IRAN
AND HOW COMMITTED THEY ARE TO THIS EFFORT AND MAKING SURE IRAN DOESN'T
AND HOW COMMITTED THEY ARE TO THIS EFFORT AND MAKING SURE IRAN DOESN'T THREATEN
AND HOW COMMITTED THEY ARE TO THIS EFFORT AND MAKING SURE IRAN DOESN'T THREATEN THEIR
AND HOW COMMITTED THEY ARE TO THIS EFFORT AND MAKING SURE IRAN DOESN'T THREATEN THEIR FAMILY
THIS EFFORT AND MAKING SURE IRAN DOESN'T THREATEN THEIR FAMILY
THIS EFFORT AND MAKING SURE IRAN DOESN'T THREATEN THEIR FAMILY WITH
THIS EFFORT AND MAKING SURE IRAN DOESN'T THREATEN THEIR FAMILY WITH A
THIS EFFORT AND MAKING SURE IRAN DOESN'T THREATEN THEIR FAMILY WITH A NUCLEAR
THIS EFFORT AND MAKING SURE IRAN DOESN'T THREATEN THEIR FAMILY WITH A NUCLEAR WEAPON.
DOESN'T THREATEN THEIR FAMILY WITH A NUCLEAR WEAPON.
DOESN'T THREATEN THEIR FAMILY WITH A NUCLEAR WEAPON. THAT
DOESN'T THREATEN THEIR FAMILY WITH A NUCLEAR WEAPON. THAT IS
DOESN'T THREATEN THEIR FAMILY WITH A NUCLEAR WEAPON. THAT IS THE
DOESN'T THREATEN THEIR FAMILY WITH A NUCLEAR WEAPON. THAT IS THE KIND
DOESN'T THREATEN THEIR FAMILY WITH A NUCLEAR WEAPON. THAT IS THE KIND OF
DOESN'T THREATEN THEIR FAMILY WITH A NUCLEAR WEAPON. THAT IS THE KIND OF INTENSITY
WITH A NUCLEAR WEAPON. THAT IS THE KIND OF INTENSITY
WITH A NUCLEAR WEAPON. THAT IS THE KIND OF INTENSITY ARE
WITH A NUCLEAR WEAPON. THAT IS THE KIND OF INTENSITY ARE WAR
WITH A NUCLEAR WEAPON. THAT IS THE KIND OF INTENSITY ARE WAR FIGHTERS
WITH A NUCLEAR WEAPON. THAT IS THE KIND OF INTENSITY ARE WAR FIGHTERS HAVE
WITH A NUCLEAR WEAPON. THAT IS THE KIND OF INTENSITY ARE WAR FIGHTERS HAVE ABOUT
THAT IS THE KIND OF INTENSITY ARE WAR FIGHTERS HAVE ABOUT
THAT IS THE KIND OF INTENSITY ARE WAR FIGHTERS HAVE ABOUT MAKING
THAT IS THE KIND OF INTENSITY ARE WAR FIGHTERS HAVE ABOUT MAKING SURE
THAT IS THE KIND OF INTENSITY ARE WAR FIGHTERS HAVE ABOUT MAKING SURE THAT
THAT IS THE KIND OF INTENSITY ARE WAR FIGHTERS HAVE ABOUT MAKING SURE THAT IRAN
THAT IS THE KIND OF INTENSITY ARE WAR FIGHTERS HAVE ABOUT MAKING SURE THAT IRAN IS
THAT IS THE KIND OF INTENSITY ARE WAR FIGHTERS HAVE ABOUT MAKING SURE THAT IRAN IS NOT
ARE WAR FIGHTERS HAVE ABOUT MAKING SURE THAT IRAN IS NOT
ARE WAR FIGHTERS HAVE ABOUT MAKING SURE THAT IRAN IS NOT CAPABLE
ARE WAR FIGHTERS HAVE ABOUT MAKING SURE THAT IRAN IS NOT CAPABLE --
MAKING SURE THAT IRAN IS NOT CAPABLE --
MAKING SURE THAT IRAN IS NOT CAPABLE -- >>
MAKING SURE THAT IRAN IS NOT CAPABLE -- >> IF
MAKING SURE THAT IRAN IS NOT CAPABLE -- >> IF YOU
MAKING SURE THAT IRAN IS NOT CAPABLE -- >> IF YOU LISTEN
MAKING SURE THAT IRAN IS NOT CAPABLE -- >> IF YOU LISTEN TO
MAKING SURE THAT IRAN IS NOT CAPABLE -- >> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY
MAKING SURE THAT IRAN IS NOT CAPABLE -- >> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS,
CAPABLE -- >> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS,
CAPABLE -- >> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS, HE
CAPABLE -- >> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS, HE WOULD
CAPABLE -- >> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS, HE WOULD HAVE
CAPABLE -- >> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS, HE WOULD HAVE HEARD
CAPABLE -- >> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS, HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME
CAPABLE -- >> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS, HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY
CAPABLE -- >> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS, HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY HOW
>> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS, HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY HOW
>> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS, HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY HOW AMAZING
>> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS, HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY HOW AMAZING OUR
>> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS, HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY HOW AMAZING OUR WAR
>> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS, HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY HOW AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS
>> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS, HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY HOW AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE
>> IF YOU LISTEN TO MY COMMENTS, HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY HOW AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE --
HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY HOW AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE --
HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY HOW AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE -- SEC.
HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY HOW AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE -- SEC. HEGSETH:
HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY HOW AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE -- SEC. HEGSETH: I
HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY HOW AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE -- SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD
HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY HOW AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE -- SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE
HE WOULD HAVE HEARD ME SAY HOW AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE -- SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE --
AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE -- SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE --
AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE -- SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE -- I
AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE -- SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE -- I HEARD
AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE -- SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE -- I HEARD EXACTLY
AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE -- SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE -- I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT
AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE -- SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE -- I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE
AMAZING OUR WAR FIGHTERS ARE -- SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE -- I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID.
SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE -- I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID.
SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE -- I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >>
SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE -- I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >> I
SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE -- I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >> I WILL
SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE -- I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >> I WILL TELL
SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE -- I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >> I WILL TELL YOU
SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE -- I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >> I WILL TELL YOU HOW
SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE -- I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >> I WILL TELL YOU HOW I
SEC. HEGSETH: I HEARD FAILURE -- I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >> I WILL TELL YOU HOW I USED
I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >> I WILL TELL YOU HOW I USED
I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >> I WILL TELL YOU HOW I USED THE
I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >> I WILL TELL YOU HOW I USED THE WORD
I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >> I WILL TELL YOU HOW I USED THE WORD FAILURE,
I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >> I WILL TELL YOU HOW I USED THE WORD FAILURE, I
I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >> I WILL TELL YOU HOW I USED THE WORD FAILURE, I USE
I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >> I WILL TELL YOU HOW I USED THE WORD FAILURE, I USE THE
I HEARD EXACTLY WHAT HE SAID. >> I WILL TELL YOU HOW I USED THE WORD FAILURE, I USE THE WORD
>> I WILL TELL YOU HOW I USED THE WORD FAILURE, I USE THE WORD
>> I WILL TELL YOU HOW I USED THE WORD FAILURE, I USE THE WORD FAILURE
>> I WILL TELL YOU HOW I USED THE WORD FAILURE, I USE THE WORD FAILURE TO
>> I WILL TELL YOU HOW I USED THE WORD FAILURE, I USE THE WORD FAILURE TO THEIR
>> I WILL TELL YOU HOW I USED THE WORD FAILURE, I USE THE WORD FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS.
THE WORD FAILURE, I USE THE WORD FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS.
THE WORD FAILURE, I USE THE WORD FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS. YOU
THE WORD FAILURE, I USE THE WORD FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS. YOU ARE
THE WORD FAILURE, I USE THE WORD FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS. YOU ARE THE
THE WORD FAILURE, I USE THE WORD FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS. YOU ARE THE FAILURE,
THE WORD FAILURE, I USE THE WORD FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS. YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT
THE WORD FAILURE, I USE THE WORD FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS. YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE
THE WORD FAILURE, I USE THE WORD FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS. YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN
FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS. YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN
FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS. YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN AND
FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS. YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN
FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS. YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN ON
FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS. YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN ON THE
FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS. YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT
FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS. YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT LINE,
FAILURE TO THEIR LEADERS. YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT LINE, NOT
YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT LINE, NOT
YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT LINE, NOT THE
YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT LINE, NOT THE MEN
YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT LINE, NOT THE MEN AND
YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT LINE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN
YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT LINE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO
YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT LINE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD
YOU ARE THE FAILURE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT LINE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD UP
AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT LINE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD UP
AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT LINE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD UP THEIR
AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT LINE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD UP THEIR HONOR
AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT LINE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD UP THEIR HONOR WITH
AND WOMEN ON THE FRONT LINE, NOT THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD UP THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION.
THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD UP THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION.
THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD UP THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION. BUT
THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD UP THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION. BUT IF
THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD UP THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION. BUT IF THERE
THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD UP THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION. BUT IF THERE IS
THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD UP THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION. BUT IF THERE IS A
THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD UP THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION. BUT IF THERE IS A LACK
THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD UP THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION. BUT IF THERE IS A LACK OF
THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO HOLD UP THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION. BUT IF THERE IS A LACK OF A
THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION. BUT IF THERE IS A LACK OF A
THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION. BUT IF THERE IS A LACK OF A WINNING
THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION. BUT IF THERE IS A LACK OF A WINNING STRATEGY,
THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION. BUT IF THERE IS A LACK OF A WINNING STRATEGY, THEY
THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION. BUT IF THERE IS A LACK OF A WINNING STRATEGY, THEY ARE
THEIR HONOR WITH DISTINCTION. BUT IF THERE IS A LACK OF A WINNING STRATEGY, THEY ARE IN
BUT IF THERE IS A LACK OF A WINNING STRATEGY, THEY ARE IN
BUT IF THERE IS A LACK OF A WINNING STRATEGY, THEY ARE IN HARM'S
BUT IF THERE IS A LACK OF A WINNING STRATEGY, THEY ARE IN HARM'S WAY,
BUT IF THERE IS A LACK OF A WINNING STRATEGY, THEY ARE IN HARM'S WAY, THEIR
BUT IF THERE IS A LACK OF A WINNING STRATEGY, THEY ARE IN HARM'S WAY, THEIR LEADERS
BUT IF THERE IS A LACK OF A WINNING STRATEGY, THEY ARE IN HARM'S WAY, THEIR LEADERS HAVE
WINNING STRATEGY, THEY ARE IN HARM'S WAY, THEIR LEADERS HAVE
WINNING STRATEGY, THEY ARE IN HARM'S WAY, THEIR LEADERS HAVE FAILED
WINNING STRATEGY, THEY ARE IN HARM'S WAY, THEIR LEADERS HAVE FAILED THEM.
HARM'S WAY, THEIR LEADERS HAVE FAILED THEM.
HARM'S WAY, THEIR LEADERS HAVE FAILED THEM. THAT
HARM'S WAY, THEIR LEADERS HAVE FAILED THEM. THAT IS
HARM'S WAY, THEIR LEADERS HAVE FAILED THEM. THAT IS WHAT
HARM'S WAY, THEIR LEADERS HAVE FAILED THEM. THAT IS WHAT IS
HARM'S WAY, THEIR LEADERS HAVE FAILED THEM. THAT IS WHAT IS HAPPENING.
FAILED THEM. THAT IS WHAT IS HAPPENING.
FAILED THEM. THAT IS WHAT IS HAPPENING. WE
FAILED THEM. THAT IS WHAT IS HAPPENING. WE HAVE
FAILED THEM. THAT IS WHAT IS HAPPENING. WE HAVE POLITICAL
FAILED THEM. THAT IS WHAT IS HAPPENING. WE HAVE POLITICAL LEADERSHIP,
THAT IS WHAT IS HAPPENING. WE HAVE POLITICAL LEADERSHIP,
THAT IS WHAT IS HAPPENING. WE HAVE POLITICAL LEADERSHIP, YOU,
THAT IS WHAT IS HAPPENING. WE HAVE POLITICAL LEADERSHIP, YOU, YOU
THAT IS WHAT IS HAPPENING. WE HAVE POLITICAL LEADERSHIP, YOU, YOU DON'T
THAT IS WHAT IS HAPPENING. WE HAVE POLITICAL LEADERSHIP, YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE
THAT IS WHAT IS HAPPENING. WE HAVE POLITICAL LEADERSHIP, YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE A
THAT IS WHAT IS HAPPENING. WE HAVE POLITICAL LEADERSHIP, YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE A STRATEGY
WE HAVE POLITICAL LEADERSHIP, YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE A STRATEGY
WE HAVE POLITICAL LEADERSHIP, YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE A STRATEGY OR
WE HAVE POLITICAL LEADERSHIP, YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE A STRATEGY OR A
WE HAVE POLITICAL LEADERSHIP, YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE A STRATEGY OR A LONG-TERM
WE HAVE POLITICAL LEADERSHIP, YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE A STRATEGY OR A LONG-TERM PLAN
WE HAVE POLITICAL LEADERSHIP, YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE A STRATEGY OR A LONG-TERM PLAN TO
WE HAVE POLITICAL LEADERSHIP, YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE A STRATEGY OR A LONG-TERM PLAN TO ACTUALLY
YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE A STRATEGY OR A LONG-TERM PLAN TO ACTUALLY
YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE A STRATEGY OR A LONG-TERM PLAN TO ACTUALLY WIN
YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE A STRATEGY OR A LONG-TERM PLAN TO ACTUALLY WIN THIS
YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE A STRATEGY OR A LONG-TERM PLAN TO ACTUALLY WIN THIS WAR.
OR A LONG-TERM PLAN TO ACTUALLY WIN THIS WAR.
OR A LONG-TERM PLAN TO ACTUALLY WIN THIS WAR. WIN
OR A LONG-TERM PLAN TO ACTUALLY WIN THIS WAR. WIN THE
OR A LONG-TERM PLAN TO ACTUALLY WIN THIS WAR. WIN THE WAR.
WIN THIS WAR. WIN THE WAR.
WIN THIS WAR. WIN THE WAR. THE
WIN THIS WAR. WIN THE WAR. THE MEN
WIN THIS WAR. WIN THE WAR. THE MEN AND
WIN THIS WAR. WIN THE WAR. THE MEN AND WOMEN
WIN THIS WAR. WIN THE WAR. THE MEN AND WOMEN WILL
WIN THIS WAR. WIN THE WAR. THE MEN AND WOMEN WILL BE
WIN THIS WAR. WIN THE WAR. THE MEN AND WOMEN WILL BE ABLE
WIN THE WAR. THE MEN AND WOMEN WILL BE ABLE
WIN THE WAR. THE MEN AND WOMEN WILL BE ABLE TO
WIN THE WAR. THE MEN AND WOMEN WILL BE ABLE TO DO
WIN THE WAR. THE MEN AND WOMEN WILL BE ABLE TO DO IT,
WIN THE WAR. THE MEN AND WOMEN WILL BE ABLE TO DO IT, BUT
WIN THE WAR. THE MEN AND WOMEN WILL BE ABLE TO DO IT, BUT THEY
WIN THE WAR. THE MEN AND WOMEN WILL BE ABLE TO DO IT, BUT THEY NEED
WIN THE WAR. THE MEN AND WOMEN WILL BE ABLE TO DO IT, BUT THEY NEED TO
WIN THE WAR. THE MEN AND WOMEN WILL BE ABLE TO DO IT, BUT THEY NEED TO HAVE
THE MEN AND WOMEN WILL BE ABLE TO DO IT, BUT THEY NEED TO HAVE
THE MEN AND WOMEN WILL BE ABLE TO DO IT, BUT THEY NEED TO HAVE LEADERSHIP.
TO DO IT, BUT THEY NEED TO HAVE LEADERSHIP.
TO DO IT, BUT THEY NEED TO HAVE LEADERSHIP. WHEN
TO DO IT, BUT THEY NEED TO HAVE LEADERSHIP. WHEN WILL
TO DO IT, BUT THEY NEED TO HAVE LEADERSHIP. WHEN WILL YOU
TO DO IT, BUT THEY NEED TO HAVE LEADERSHIP. WHEN WILL YOU SHOW
TO DO IT, BUT THEY NEED TO HAVE LEADERSHIP. WHEN WILL YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP?
LEADERSHIP. WHEN WILL YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP?
LEADERSHIP. WHEN WILL YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP? SEC.
LEADERSHIP. WHEN WILL YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP? SEC. HEGSETH:
LEADERSHIP. WHEN WILL YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP? SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE
LEADERSHIP. WHEN WILL YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP? SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE YOU
LEADERSHIP. WHEN WILL YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP? SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE YOU SHOW
WHEN WILL YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP? SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE YOU SHOW
WHEN WILL YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP? SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP
WHEN WILL YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP? SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP AND
WHEN WILL YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP? SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP AND STAND
WHEN WILL YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP? SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP AND STAND UP
WHEN WILL YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP? SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP AND STAND UP TO
WHEN WILL YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP? SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP AND STAND UP TO YOUR
SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP AND STAND UP TO YOUR
SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP AND STAND UP TO YOUR FELLOW
SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP AND STAND UP TO YOUR FELLOW DEMOCRATS
SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP AND STAND UP TO YOUR FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO
SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP AND STAND UP TO YOUR FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO WON'T
SEC. HEGSETH: WHILE YOU SHOW LEADERSHIP AND STAND UP TO YOUR FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO WON'T FUND
LEADERSHIP AND STAND UP TO YOUR FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO WON'T FUND
LEADERSHIP AND STAND UP TO YOUR FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO WON'T FUND THE
LEADERSHIP AND STAND UP TO YOUR FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO WON'T FUND THE TROOPS,
LEADERSHIP AND STAND UP TO YOUR FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO WON'T FUND THE TROOPS, WHO
LEADERSHIP AND STAND UP TO YOUR FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO WON'T FUND THE TROOPS, WHO PLAY
LEADERSHIP AND STAND UP TO YOUR FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO WON'T FUND THE TROOPS, WHO PLAY PARTISAN
FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO WON'T FUND THE TROOPS, WHO PLAY PARTISAN
FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO WON'T FUND THE TROOPS, WHO PLAY PARTISAN PART
FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO WON'T FUND THE TROOPS, WHO PLAY PARTISAN PART --
FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO WON'T FUND THE TROOPS, WHO PLAY PARTISAN PART -- POLITICS
FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO WON'T FUND THE TROOPS, WHO PLAY PARTISAN PART -- POLITICS WHILE
FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO WON'T FUND THE TROOPS, WHO PLAY PARTISAN PART -- POLITICS WHILE YOU
FELLOW DEMOCRATS WHO WON'T FUND THE TROOPS, WHO PLAY PARTISAN PART -- POLITICS WHILE YOU DON'T
THE TROOPS, WHO PLAY PARTISAN PART -- POLITICS WHILE YOU DON'T
THE TROOPS, WHO PLAY PARTISAN PART -- POLITICS WHILE YOU DON'T GIVE
THE TROOPS, WHO PLAY PARTISAN PART -- POLITICS WHILE YOU DON'T GIVE US
THE TROOPS, WHO PLAY PARTISAN PART -- POLITICS WHILE YOU DON'T GIVE US THE
THE TROOPS, WHO PLAY PARTISAN PART -- POLITICS WHILE YOU DON'T GIVE US THE MONEY.
PART -- POLITICS WHILE YOU DON'T GIVE US THE MONEY.
PART -- POLITICS WHILE YOU DON'T GIVE US THE MONEY. YOU
PART -- POLITICS WHILE YOU DON'T GIVE US THE MONEY. YOU WANT
PART -- POLITICS WHILE YOU DON'T GIVE US THE MONEY. YOU WANT TO
PART -- POLITICS WHILE YOU DON'T GIVE US THE MONEY. YOU WANT TO TALK
PART -- POLITICS WHILE YOU DON'T GIVE US THE MONEY. YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT
PART -- POLITICS WHILE YOU DON'T GIVE US THE MONEY. YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE
GIVE US THE MONEY. YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE
GIVE US THE MONEY. YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE TROOPS
GIVE US THE MONEY. YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE TROOPS --
YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE TROOPS --
YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE TROOPS -- TO
YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE TROOPS -- TO FUND
YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE TROOPS -- TO FUND OUR
YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE TROOPS -- TO FUND OUR DEPARTMENT,
YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE TROOPS -- TO FUND OUR DEPARTMENT, BECAUSE
TROOPS -- TO FUND OUR DEPARTMENT, BECAUSE
TROOPS -- TO FUND OUR DEPARTMENT, BECAUSE YOU
TROOPS -- TO FUND OUR DEPARTMENT, BECAUSE YOU HAVE
TROOPS -- TO FUND OUR DEPARTMENT, BECAUSE YOU HAVE TRUMP
TROOPS -- TO FUND OUR DEPARTMENT, BECAUSE YOU HAVE TRUMP DERANGEMENT
TO FUND OUR DEPARTMENT, BECAUSE YOU HAVE TRUMP DERANGEMENT
TO FUND OUR DEPARTMENT, BECAUSE YOU HAVE TRUMP DERANGEMENT SYNDROME
TO FUND OUR DEPARTMENT, BECAUSE YOU HAVE TRUMP DERANGEMENT SYNDROME AND
TO FUND OUR DEPARTMENT, BECAUSE YOU HAVE TRUMP DERANGEMENT SYNDROME AND CAN'T
TO FUND OUR DEPARTMENT, BECAUSE YOU HAVE TRUMP DERANGEMENT SYNDROME AND CAN'T ACTUALLY
YOU HAVE TRUMP DERANGEMENT SYNDROME AND CAN'T ACTUALLY
YOU HAVE TRUMP DERANGEMENT SYNDROME AND CAN'T ACTUALLY COMMIT
YOU HAVE TRUMP DERANGEMENT SYNDROME AND CAN'T ACTUALLY COMMIT TO
YOU HAVE TRUMP DERANGEMENT SYNDROME AND CAN'T ACTUALLY COMMIT TO ANYTHING
YOU HAVE TRUMP DERANGEMENT SYNDROME AND CAN'T ACTUALLY COMMIT TO ANYTHING MEANINGFUL.
SYNDROME AND CAN'T ACTUALLY COMMIT TO ANYTHING MEANINGFUL.
SYNDROME AND CAN'T ACTUALLY COMMIT TO ANYTHING MEANINGFUL. I
SYNDROME AND CAN'T ACTUALLY COMMIT TO ANYTHING MEANINGFUL. I PUT
SYNDROME AND CAN'T ACTUALLY COMMIT TO ANYTHING MEANINGFUL. I PUT THIS
SYNDROME AND CAN'T ACTUALLY COMMIT TO ANYTHING MEANINGFUL. I PUT THIS ON
SYNDROME AND CAN'T ACTUALLY COMMIT TO ANYTHING MEANINGFUL. I PUT THIS ON YOU,
SYNDROME AND CAN'T ACTUALLY COMMIT TO ANYTHING MEANINGFUL. I PUT THIS ON YOU, SENATOR.
COMMIT TO ANYTHING MEANINGFUL. I PUT THIS ON YOU, SENATOR.
COMMIT TO ANYTHING MEANINGFUL. I PUT THIS ON YOU, SENATOR. >>
COMMIT TO ANYTHING MEANINGFUL. I PUT THIS ON YOU, SENATOR. >> YOU
COMMIT TO ANYTHING MEANINGFUL. I PUT THIS ON YOU, SENATOR. >> YOU HAVE
COMMIT TO ANYTHING MEANINGFUL. I PUT THIS ON YOU, SENATOR. >> YOU HAVE OVER
COMMIT TO ANYTHING MEANINGFUL. I PUT THIS ON YOU, SENATOR. >> YOU HAVE OVER $1
COMMIT TO ANYTHING MEANINGFUL. I PUT THIS ON YOU, SENATOR. >> YOU HAVE OVER $1 TRILLION,
I PUT THIS ON YOU, SENATOR. >> YOU HAVE OVER $1 TRILLION,
I PUT THIS ON YOU, SENATOR. >> YOU HAVE OVER $1 TRILLION, YOU
I PUT THIS ON YOU, SENATOR. >> YOU HAVE OVER $1 TRILLION, YOU ARE
I PUT THIS ON YOU, SENATOR. >> YOU HAVE OVER $1 TRILLION, YOU ARE ASKING